swelen.com 2015-06-07

# Swelen - Privacy Policy

Swelen is a digital market place that allows publishers to monetize their website or application, through advertisements. In order to pay our publishers for a display, a click or a sale, we have to record, via cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies some actions made ​​on the websites. 

We may also collect your device identifier, IP address or identifier for advertising (IDFA), which may be used to tailor the advertising you see on our publishers websites as well as for statistical analysis and targeting. 

User actions that are collected are displays and clicks on our advertisements but also actions such as application downloads. Nor do we store personal data with cross-reference to these actions. All data is anonymous and is not shared with third parties. 

If you want to delete all cookies that we could save on your browser, you can use the embedded function to remove the cookies from the domain swelen.com. If you do not want our system raises other cookies on your browser you can visit our [deleting cookies section](http://www.swelen.com/?unsubscribe).

### Personally Identifiable Information

Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) is data about you that is personally identifiable. Examples of personally identifiable information include name, address, email address, credit card number or any other information that is not otherwise publicly available.

We at swelen don't use any PII at anytime.

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“NPII”) data is collected by Swelen and our partners and is used for retargeting. We may collect NPII from people who visit our clients’ websites.

This data is anonymous, and can include information such as web pages you’ve viewed, date and time of pageviews, domain type, location information associated with your IP address, and your interactions to an ad delivered by us or our ad technology partners.

Swelen use different methods to collect this type of data, including cookies and web beacons, and it is stored indefinitely.

### Swelen's Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

Cookies are small text files that can store information. There are two types of cookies: session cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies expire when you close your browser, and persistent cookies stay on your computer until you delete them. Swelen may use both session and persistent cookies to customize your web experience and to analyze web traffic. Swelen uses cookies and web beacons in the delivery of display advertisements to our clients’ website visitors on various websites. This is how the process works:

You visit our client’s website. Our web beacon fires and drops a persistent cookie onto your browser. When you leave the client’s website and visit a second website, Swelen ad technology are able to recognize that browser cookie and serve a display ad to you. These cookies do not store any PII, but they do record the following information: the set of people cookied, websites visited, where and when people viewed our ads, interactions (such as clicks) with an ad, and if a purchase was made. This type of information can in no way be used to identify a specific person or user of our service. This data will never be shared with third parties or used to display ads for a third party without explicit written permission from all parties.

The NPII collected by Swelen in the aforementioned process will be kept by Swelen indefinitely and will be securely maintained and archived. Swelen does not link the NPII described here to any personally identifiable information provided to us.

We believe everyone should have control over which ads they see, and we allow anyone to opt out from being served retargeted ads by or through Swelen’s service. If you use multiple browsers or devices, you will need to opt out on each browser or device, and if you delete your cookies you will need to opt out again.

### Removing on IOS

First, iOS 7 has started using an Advertising Identifier, a “non-permanent device identifier” that allows Swelen to track your device over time through apps that you use.

Inside the Privacy > Advertising menu, you’ll find two options. The first, “Limit Ad Tracking,” means that Swelen won’t be able to use the Advertising Identifier to track you on your iPhone, iPad or iPod Touch.

The second, allows you to reset your Advertising ID.

If you prefer personalized ads, you might want to leave it on.

### Removing on Android

To reset your advertising ID on your Android device, follow the below procedure :

Go to Apps > Google Settings > Ads, Tap on “Reset advertising ID“
